一名身着明代书生袍的男子在夜晚独自穿行于黑暗的松林中，手持纸灯笼。
A man in traditional Ming Dynasty scholar's robes walks alone through a dark pine forest at night, holding a paper lantern.
他脸色惊恐，似乎在回忆某个可怕的事件。
He looks terrified, seemingly recalling a horrifying event.
镜头切换到一位身穿华丽服装的女士，她站在夜色中的庭院里，神情严肃，周围有手持长矛的侍卫。
The scene shifts to a lady in elaborate attire standing in a moonlit courtyard, looking serious, with guards holding spears in the background.
男子在黑暗中悄悄进入一座传统建筑。
The man furtively enters a traditional building in the dark.
夜色中的花园，女子身穿淡雅的衣袍，缓缓走下台阶。
In the dark garden, the woman in light, elegant robes slowly descends the steps.
她穿过石桥，似乎在等待什么。
She crosses a stone bridge, appearing to wait for something.
之前身着书生袍的男子从树后探出头来，偷偷观察着她。
The man in scholar's robes peeks out from behind a tree, secretly observing her.
一位年长的男子从高处俯视，他面带疑惑。
An older man looks down from a higher floor, his face showing confusion.
女子回到门口，显得焦躁不安。
The woman returns to the doorway, appearing restless.
她焦急地踱步，眼神不时望向黑暗深处。
She paces anxiously, her gaze frequently sweeping into the darkness.
女子徘徊在庭院中，她的不安感越来越强。
The woman wanders in the courtyard, her unease growing.
她穿过拱门，眼神中带着期待和不安。
She passes through an archway, her eyes showing both anticipation and apprehension.
女子在夜色中继续前行，仿佛在寻找什么。
The woman continues walking through the night, as if searching for something.
书生跪在地上挖土，女子站在一旁，表情担忧。
The scholar kneels on the ground, digging, while the woman stands nearby, looking concerned.
年长的男子从石柱后露出头，神色警惕地看着。
The older man peeks out from behind a stone pillar, watching with a wary expression.
女子走近书生，脸上带着明显的担忧。
The woman approaches the scholar, her face showing clear concern.
她伸出手，试图阻止书生。
She extends her hand, trying to stop the scholar.
书生抬起头，脸上露出羞愧和贪婪交织的复杂表情。
The scholar looks up, his face a complex mix of shame and greed.
书生起身，背对女子，似乎准备离开。
The scholar stands up, his back to the woman, seemingly preparing to leave.
女子抓住他的手，恳求他。
The woman grabs his hand, pleading with him.
书生试图甩开她的手，脸上露出凶狠的神色。
The scholar tries to shake off her hand, a fierce expression on his face.
书生猛地推开女子，女子踉跄后退。
The scholar abruptly pushes the woman away, causing her to stumble backward.
书生再次粗暴地推搡女子，女子倒地。
The scholar roughly shoves the woman again, and she falls to the ground.
女子倒在地上，书生转身逃离。
The woman lies on the ground, and the scholar turns and flees.
女子试图爬起来追赶，但书生再次将她推倒，然后消失在黑暗中。
The woman tries to get up and chase him, but the scholar pushes her down again and disappears into the darkness.
女子倒在地上，无助地呼喊。
The woman lies on the ground, crying out helplessly.
男子再次面对镜头，脸上带着得意和狡黠的笑容。
The man faces the camera again, a triumphant and cunning smile on his face.